Guide to the Consolidation Coal Company Records, 1854-1971 AIS.2011.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Secretary's Contract Files, VI.
  - Robert McKnight et. ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., January 19, 1883; 832.
  - William B. Linhart and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Company, September 10, 1874; 833.
  - Emanuel Stotler, December 2, 1811-June 23, 1886; 834.
  - Charles Myers and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 13, 1909; 835.
  - Eveline Wright et. ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 22, 1909; 836.
  - Joseph F. Wallace et. al. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 15, 1909; 837.
  - James Briggs and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, August 31, 1909; 838.
  - George Z. Hosack, agent for PCC and Vencil Lulla et. ux., September 29, 1909; 839.
  - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 27, 1909; 841.
  - Elkins Gas Coal Co. and Westmoreland Coal Co., April 3, 1895; 842.
  - George Z. Hosack, agent for PCC and Paul Kosmach, September 24, 1909; 843.
  - C. L. Snowden & S. S. Graham, Trustees of the estate of Adam Jacobs, September 23, 1909; 848.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 24, 1909; 849.
  - United Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, July 1, 1905-February 28, 1912; 851 A-C.
  - United Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, February 28, 1912-February 28, 1919; 851 D-F.
  - J. N. Kerr and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 14, 1909; 852.
  - Sarah L. Hershey and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 18, 1909; 854.
  - Joseph W. Wolfe and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 21, 1909; 855.
  - T. T. Gillespie and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 25, 1909; 856.
  - Johnston Farm Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 15, 1909; 857.
  - G. Dauenhauer & Sons Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 4, 1909; 858.
  - South West Pennsylvania Pipe Lines and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 29, 1902; 859.
  - Canadian Northern Coal & Ore Dock Co., June 1, 1906; 860.
  - Ohio Coal Co. (of Wisconsin)-January 25, 1902 & July 15, 1931, 861.
  - William H. Hyde and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), November 3-11, 1909; 863.
  - William D. McCrory and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 9, 1909-June 1, 1910; 864.
  - Mrs. Charity Anderson et. al. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 10, 1909; 867.
  - Mary McKenna and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 10, 1919; 869.
  - H.C. Casebar and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 30, 1909; 870.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Margaret Wilson, November 29, 1905; 872.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, Alva M. Walters and L. H. Frasher, November 17, 1909; 873. (Box 50)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 20, 1910; 876.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 20, 1910; 877.
  - John Hershey, et ux. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, December 2, 1909; 879.
  - Mansfield Coal & Coke Co. and Robert S. Chess et al., October 10, 1907; 880.
  - Thomas Cook, et al. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 3, 1910; 881.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Westmoreland & Fayette Telephone Co., December 27, 1909; 882.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Wallace E. Jumper et ux., January 27, 1910-October 31, 1912; 883.
  - Joseph W. Wolfe & Son and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 27, 1910; 884.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., January 21, 1910; 885.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Cyrus E. Woods, January 28, 1910; 887.
  - Consolidated Gas Co. of N.Y. and Michael & John Tracey, February 3, 1910; 888.
  - John A. Cook et ux. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 20, 1910; 889.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and M. L. Ramaley, June 18, 1910; 891.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Isabelle Speelman, February 28, 1910; 892.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Robert W. Speelman, February 28, 1910; 893.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Samuel Welsh, February 23, 1910-May 28, 1913; 895.
  - Manor Real Estate & Trust Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, February 18, 1910-February 23, 1911; 897.
  - The Bradstreet Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 1, 1910-March 14, 1914; 898.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 30, 1909; 899.
  - Barnes Laundry Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 24, 1910; 900.
  - Pennsylvania Water Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 11, 1910; 901.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and John Adolph Schaub, July 14, 1909; 903.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and W. W. Luce, April 18, 1910; 904.
  - Dawson Construction Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, April 14, 1910; 905.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., March 29, 1910; 907.
  - Samuel M. and Mary E. Riddle and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 30, 1910; 908.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 1904; 910.
  - Murrysville Telephone Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 23, 1910-April 4, 1924; 911.
  - H.F. Stark and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 16, 1910; 912.
  - South Pittsburgh Water Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 10, 1910; 913.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and W. K. Field, May 25, 1910; 914.
  - T. D. Gladden et ux. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, May 17, 1910; 915.
  - Frank J. Morrone and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 13, 1910; 916.
  - Central District & Printing Telegraph Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, March 12, 1910; 917.
  - Emma U. Brown and C. M. Underhill, June 23, 1910; 918.
  - Emma U. Slee and C. M. Underhill, June 15, 1910; 919.
  - P. J. Mc Call and West End Coal & Coke Co., August 11, 1908; 921.
  - John A. Englert and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 1, 1909; 922.
  - Baltimore & Ohio RR Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 20, 1910; 923.
  - Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Co. and Mansfield Coal & Coke Co., October 22, 1908; 926.
  - Mansfield Coal & Coke Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), November 1891-July 6, 1892; 927.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and W. H. Graham, December 27, 1895; 930.
  - J.A. Suter and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 4, 1910; 931.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Commissioners of Wilkins Township, June 3, 1910; 934.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Crucible Steel Co., March 25, 1909; 935.
  - Pennsylvania Co. and The American Trimming Co., March 31, 1910-April 1, 1920; 936.
  - Duquesne Towel & Supply Co., May 10, 1910; 937.
  - Black Diamond Co., July 27, 1910; 938.
  - Coal Trade Co., July 28, 1910; 939.
  - The Retail Coalman, July 27, 1910; 940.
  - The Coal Trade Journal, August 1, 1910; 941.
  - Andrew G. Smith and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, July 13, 1910; 943.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 10, 1909-February 9, 1910; 944.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Co., April 6, 1908; 945.
  - Mrs. Evaline Hall and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 1, 1893; 947.
  - Ellen M. Chalfant, Liberty Coal Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., January 17- 31, 1902; 948.
  - Ellen M. Chalfant, et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 7, 1907; 949.
  - Joseph Lovett and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 14, 1908; 950. (Box 51)
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and W. G. Lane, August 2, 1902; 951.
  - Robert P. Linhart et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 28, 1903; 952.
  - Robert & John M. Kirkpatrick and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 8, 1903; 953.
  - William F. Kenny and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 31, 1899; 954.
  - Gustav Klein and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 9, 1903; 955.
  - J. G. Hamblin and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 10, 1908; 956.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Alexander Gordon Estate, October 28, 1905; 957.
  - William H. Graham, April 2, 1907; 958.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and M. Graner, July 22, 1880; 959.
  - Michael Graver, Deceased and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 15, 1886; 960.
  - Harry E. Geisler et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 29, 1902; 961.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Equitable Gas Co., May 17, 1889; 962.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Enterprise Brick & Stone Co., December 1, 1904; 963.
  - Duquesne Coal Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 1-August 13, 1879; 964.
  - James Daugherty et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 11, 1906; 965.
  - S. W. Mc Dermitt and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., January 1, 1904; 966.
  - Dickson, Stewart & Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 8, 1872; 967.
  - John Duff et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 15, 1896-April 15, 1899; 968.
  - Peter Double and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., June 24, 1887; 969.
  - Church Hill Cemetary Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 18, 1882-April 9, 1902; 970.
  - Dr. William M. Caruthers Estate and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 17, 1901-January 15, 1921; 971.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and J. B. Corey, May 5, 1885; 973.
  - Ralph & Robert Collins et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 4, 1903; 974.
  - Robert Clark, Sr. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., August 26, 1879; 975.
  - H. R. Chalfant Heirs and A. O. Tinstman (assigned to New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co.), January 31, 1903; 976.
  - Borough of Edgewood and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 14, 1901; 977. (Oversize 128)
  - Monasses S. Boyle and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co, October 18, 1906; 978. (Box 51)
  - Eli W. Boyd et ux and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 2, 1883; 979.
  - Bessemer & Lake Erie RR Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), April 27, 1905; 980.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and John Alexander Estate, March 15, 1893; 981.
  - David A. Anderson et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 31, 1903; 983.
  - Lawrence Barckhoff and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., January 6, 1908; 984.
  - William Johnston and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 10, 1884; 985.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Ann Shaughnessy et al., June 29, 1908; 987.
  - Coal & Coke Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 7, 1910; 988.
  - Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., May 31, 1910; 990.
  - Central Distirct & Printing Telegraph Co., December 23, 1907-November 11, 1912; 991.
  - W. L. Johnson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 6, 1910; 992.
  - W. L. Johnson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), September 6-9, 1910; 993 A.
  - W. L. Johnson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), September 6, 1910; 993 B.
  - W. L. Johnson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), September 6, 1910; 993 C.
  - W. L. Johnson and Citizens Savings & Trust Co., September 6, 1910; 993 D.
  - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 26, 1910; 995.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and A. L. Sampson and Bernhardt Hormel, October 13, 1910; 1000.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and William E. Harmon, September 27, 1910; 1001.
  - D. J. Riffle and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 19, 1910; 1002.
  - Joseph W. Wolfe and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 11, 1910; 1003.
  - Mansfield Coal & Coke Co. and Samuel Allinder et al., October 10, 1907; 1004.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., August 18, 1910; 1005.
  - Joseph N. Robbins and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, October 10, 1910; 1006.
  - Bollinger-Andrews Construction Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 2, 1910; 1008.
  - Allegheny County Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 28, 1910; 1019.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Edmund R. Weise, October 26, 1910; 1021.
  - William Snyder et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., January 27, 1887; 1023.
  - Jacob & Minnie Gabriel and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 6, 1902-April 26, 1912; 1024.
  - James Gray et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 25, 1886; 1025.
  - James Armstrong and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 18, 1901; 1026.
  - James Armstrong and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., June 19, 1903; 1027.
  - August Miller and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 10, 1906; 1028.
  - John Morrone and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., November 1, 1897; 1029.
  - Ephraim Hays Estate and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 30, 1886; 1030.
  - Mrs. Kate Bartley and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 31, 1910; 1031.
  - J. B. Morgan Estate and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 31, 1910; 1032.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Albert Hideck, November 23-December 30, 1910; 1034.
  - H. W. Leonard and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), December 14, 1910; 1035.
  - Industrial Index Publishing Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 18, 1901; 1036.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and James T. Fox, November 23, 1910; 1037.
  - Old Colony Building-Herbert M. Sears (Trustee) and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 6, 1910; 1038.
  - William J. Fryer and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, December 16, 1910; 1039.
  - Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co. and Clarkson Coal & Dock Co., November 1, 1910; 1040.
  - Pennsylvania Water Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Cal Co., November 3, 1908; 1042.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Perry Iron Co. of Erie, December 15, 1910; 1043.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Canada Cement Co., Ltd., October 19, 1910; 1044.
  - Baltimore & Ohio RR Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 22, 1910; 1045.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and The Turtle Creek Land & Improvement Co., April 1, 1907; 1046.
  - West Penn Electric Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 1, 1911; 1047.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, August 8, 1931; 1049.
  - Charleroi Telephone Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, February 21, 1911; 1054. (Box 52)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Metal Poster Co., May 27, 1930; 1055.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Westmoreland-Fayette Telephone Co., December 2, 1910; 1056.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and W. K. Thompson, June 23, 1910; 1060.
  - Antony Colangelo and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, February 20, 1911; 1062.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Illinois, December 31, 1923-December 4, 1942; 1065-1.
  - H.W. Oliver Estate, Pittsburgh Coal Co., and F.C. Smith, February 10, 1911; 1066.
  - John Birkham, January 31, 1911; 1068.
  - T.H. McGraw, Jr. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, January 18, 1911; 1070.
  - Mitchell & Co., January 23, 1911; 1072.
  - American Slavonic Gazette, January 28, 1911; 1073.
  - Brieck Brothers Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), March 31-August 5, 1911; 1075.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Central District & Printing Telegraph Co., March 1, 1911; 1078.
  - Stiers Lewis and M. R. Allen, Trustee of Thomas McFarland Estate, December 24, 1894-March 21, 1911; 1080.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Grant Thomas, April 17, 1911; 1081.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Andrew Robertson, March 10, 1911; 1082.
  - Pittsburgh, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, April 26, 1911; 1087.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Philadelphia Co., April 19, 1911; 1088.
  - Mary S. Baysinger and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, April 6, 1901; 1089.
  - Antony Colangelo and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, May 5, 1911; 1090.
  - Antony Colangelo and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 5, 1911; 1091.
  - A. W. Horton Estate, James McDonald and Frank Sobota, March 15, 1911; 1092.
  - Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 13, 1911; 1093.
  - Hennepin Holding Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Wisconsin, March 27, 1911; 1094.
  - William J. McCracken, Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 31, 1911; 1097.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, April 11-May 29, 1911; 1098.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Thomas Ceney et ux., April 26, 1911; 1099.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Minech & Philips, May 6, 1911; 1100.
  - Fayette Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, April 26, 1911; 1101.
  - Steel Co. of Canada Ltd., February 8, 1911; 1102.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, John W. Bell and Robert Wilson Bell, December 13, 1904; 1106.
  - Anna Zeller Watson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, November 17, 1909; 1109.
  - Mrs. Jane Marshall and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 19, 1910; 1110.
  - Joseph H. Morrow and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 6, 1908-May 13, 1914; 1113.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and William J. Athey, July 12, 1911; 1114.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and John Dimsar, July 12, 1911; 1116.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and John Telban, November 9, 1911; 1122.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and John F. Howley & Co., July 1, 1911; 1125.
  - Benjamin Kelley Morrow, John Andrew Morrow and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 15, 1895; 1126.
  - Henry Morrow and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 27, 1879; 1127.
  - W. J. Willoughby and Richard Baxter, June 14, 1911; 1131.
  - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway Co., Ashtabula Dock Co., Pickands-Mather Co., Pittsburgh Coal Co., and Pittsburgh & Conneaut Dock Co., August 10, 1910; 1132.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and W. F. Wager, September 29, 1911; 1133.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Dominion of Canada, August 29, 1911; 1134.
  - Second National Building Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 29, 1911; 1135.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Henry Northey, June 22, 1911; 1140.
  - John Matis and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 27, 1883; 1141.
  - Sarah A. McGuire et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 26, 1902; 1142.
  - Barney McGoldrick and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 27, 1887; 1143.
  - Margaret & William J. McCulley and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 30, 1906; 1144.
  - Robert McConnell et ux. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 27, 1906; 1145.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Joel Greiss, Guardian for June Ramsden, May 5, 1879; 1146.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Turtle Creek Land & Improvement Co., September 1, 1904; 1147.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 28, 1899; 1149.
  - Robert McGregor et ux., John Peterman and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 31, 1890; 1150.
  - Jesse & George Morris and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 10, 1878; 1151.
  - Christ Nehrig and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 11, 1893; 1152.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Vencil Sedina, November 8, 1911; 1153.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and David A. Miller, April 22, 1892; 1160.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 2, 1869-October 10, 1908; 1161.
  - Colonial Coke Co. and Germer Stove Co., March 28, 1911; 1164.
  - Henry Reiter and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 16, 1878; 1165.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and William A. Robb, November 15, 1901; 1166.
  - James E. & Rollo R. Stotler, James McJenkins, Guardian and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., June 16, 1906; 1167.
  - James A. Sharp and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., December 14, 1904-February 24, 1905; 1168.
  - Robert Sharp and W. B. Rath, August 6, 1904; 1169.
  - David Shaw and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 12, 1875; 1170.
  - William Schneider and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., July 6, 1891; 1171.
  - George Schneider and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 24, 1890; 1172.
  - Hussey, Howe & Co., Ltd. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 5, 1887; 1173.
  - Isabella Speelman and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., February 13, 1876; 1174.
  - A. Blair Thaw et al. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., April 27, 1893; 1176.
  - Matthew Taylor and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., September 18, 1876; 1177. (Oversize 128)
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co. and Wilson, Walker & Co., July 1, 1883; 1180. (Box 52)
  - Wilmerding Supply Co. and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., October 19, 1903; 1181.
  - Bridget Wolfe and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., May 7, 1903; 1182.
  - George D. Whitcomb and New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., August 7, 1883; 1183. (Box 53)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Louis Godfrey et ux., October 1, 1931; 1193.
  - E. E. Patterson and John A. Black, December 7, 1911; 1200.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Minnie McChancey, January 1, 1912; 1201.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Ann C. Baker, September 27, 1909; 1202.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. Stockholders, February 21, 1901-March 24, 1928; 1205.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and John W. Johnen, February 28, 1912; 1210.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Michael Harvath, January 19, 1912; 1211.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, March 4, 1902; 1212.
  - Dravo Contracting Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), March 14, 1912; 1214.
  - Lee & Hamilton Coal Co. (Lee & Hamilton, Inc.), January 10, 1905-March 28, 1914; 1217.
  - Saw Mill Run Coal & Supply Co., November 6, 1902-March 16, 1914; 1218.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph McMurray, April 1, 1912; 1219.
  - Edward J. House and Saw Mill Run Coal & Supply Co., March 30, 1910; 1220.
  - South Pittsburgh Water Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 23, 1911; 1221.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Otto Georgi et ux., March 12, 1912; 1225.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Frank Bouma, March 27, 1912; 1229.
  - Alice B. Phillips, April 22, 1912; 1230.
  - New York & Cleveland Gas Coal Co., March 24, 1883-September 1, 1904; 1231.
  - Freda H. and John Low and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, February 28, 1912; 1236.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Dr. C. N. VanSickle, April 24, 1912; 1238.
  - Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Co. and Soo-River Coal Isle Co., June 20, 1912; 1255.
  - Robert S. and George M. Todd, et ux and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, July 24, 1912; 1256.
  - New York Central RR Co., Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 1, 1912-October 27, 1922; 1259.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and Philadelphia Co, June 29, 1912; 1261.
  - John W. Phillips and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, July 31, 1912; 1267.
  - The Ontario Coal & Supply Co., August 11, 1910-June 2, 1914; 1273. (Oversize 128)
  - James Allingham and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, September 11, 1912-January 29, 1913; 1277. (Box 53)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania and David Strang, September 25, 1917; 1282.
  - Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway Co., Edward Gillen Dredge Dock & Construction Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 1, 1912-June 19, 1917; 1287.
  - Westmoreland Coal Co. and Elkins Gas Coal Co., July 25, 1901; 1293.
  - Cleveland & Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 26, 1869; 1294.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank J. Hurl, September 25, 1931; 1296.